Katsi Cook Papers, 1977-2008
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IX. SUBJECT FILES
  - Ecosystem Health and Remedial Action Plans (RAP)
  - Environmental Contamination
  - Environmental Contamination and Animal Health
  - Environmental Contamination and Human Health (Box 7)
  - Environmental Contamination and Mental Health/Social Impacts
  - Health, general (Box 8)
  - Menopause
  - Midwifery
  - Research Protocols
  - Traditional Ecological Knowledge
  - Workshops
- AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS
  - Computer disks (Box 9)
  - Audiovisual materials (Box 10)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Posters and photographs, 2000, n.d.; Daybreak Vol 2, Issue I, midwinter 1988; Healing Words, Vol 2, No.1, Fall 20001998, 2000 (Map-case Flat File Drawer 21)
  - Akwasasne Notes Vol. 8 No. 2, Early Summer, 1976; Vol. 9, No. 5, Dec 19771976-77 (Map-case Flat File Drawer 21)